

Babur Shah Sayer

Nationality: Afghan (+93) 789883431

Date of birth: 15 Dec 1999

Gender: Male

Email address: babursayer@gmail.com

Website: www.baburshahsayer.com

Skype: Babur Shah Sayer

LinkedIn: https://af.linkedin.com/in/babur-shah-sayer-79b0161b1

• Address: Old Taimani Square, Across Kardan University, Kabul Afghanistan, 1010 Kabul (Afgh

anistan)

ABOUT ME

Hi! I'm a front-end web developer with a passion for slashing innovation and appealing design. Over my two years of Web Development experience, I have had major manufacturers accomplishments, such as design, document, and construct some of the most important applications and websites using cutting-edge development tools, methodologies, and resources. I've learned how to create amazing ties with all divisions into an organization through either experience. I can work duopoly and above companies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Administrative assistant

SMF Group International [4 Apr 2018 – 18 Apr 2020]

City: Kabul

Country: Afghanistan

Ensure operation of equipment by completing preventive maintenance requirements; calling for repairs; maintaining equipment inventories; evaluating new equipment and techniques

Contribute to team effort by accomplishing related results as needed

Carry out administrative duties such as filing, typing, copying, binding, scanning, etc.

Organize travel arrangements for senior managers

Write letters and emails on behalf of other office staff

Book conference calls, rooms, taxis, couriers, hotels, etc.

Cover the reception desk when required

Reply to email, telephone, or face to face inquiries

Develop and update administrative systems to make them more efficient

Web Applications Development Intern

Web Applications Development Intern

ThePros [8 Jun 2020 - 31 Dec 2020]

City: Kabul

Country: Afghanistan

Designing and implementing Java-based applications. Analyzing user requirements to inform application design. Ensuring continuous professional self-development. Defining application objectives and functionality. Aligning application design with business goals. Developing and testing software. Debugging and resolving technical problems that arise.

Front-End Web developer

Honesthelper [9 Mar 2021 - Current]

City: Kabul

Country: Afghanistan

Use markup languages like HTML to create user-friendly web pages

Maintain and improve website

Optimize applications for maximum speed

Design mobile-based features

Collaborate with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability

Get feedback from, and build solutions for, users and customers

Write functional requirement documents and guides

Help back-end developers with coding and troubleshooting

Ensure high quality graphic standards and brand consistency

Stay up-to-date on emerging technologies

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

(BSE) Bachelor Of Software Engineering

Rana University [12 Nov 2017 – 25 Nov 2021]

Address: Baraki Square, Kabul Afghanistan, 1010 Kabul (Afghanistan)

High School

Abdul Hadi Davi High School [1 Mar 2005 - 3 Jun 2017]

Address: District 9 near the 3rd Mikrorayon, Kabul Afghanistan, 1007 Kabul (Afghanistan)

DEL

Plan Future Institute [10 Feb 2019 – 12 Feb 2020]

Address: Qalai Fathullah 8 Main Road - Kabul, Afghanistan, 1003 Kabul (Afghanistan)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Persian

Other language(s):

Persian	Pachte
Persian	Pashto

LISTENING C2 READING C2 WRITING C2 LISTENING C1 READING B1 WRITING B1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C2 SPOKEN INTERACTION C2 SPOKEN PRODUCTION C2 SPOKEN INTERACTION C2

English Urdu

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1 LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1 SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1

DIGITAL SKILLS

HTML / CSS / SCSS / Bootstrap / Figma / Adobe Photoshop / MySQL / Git / Github / Javascript / PHP / Laravel Framework / Linux